我记得
I remember.
我全都记得
I remember everything.
韦伯上尉 早上好
Captain Webb. Good morning.
有人给你解释过一切了吗
Has everything been explained to you?
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
等结束以后 你就不再是大卫·韦伯了
When we are finished with you, you will no longer be David Webb.
你想让我变成谁都行 长官
I'll be whoever you need me to be, sir.
你完全清楚 选择留下意味着什么
You knew exactly what it meant for you if you chose to stay.
你不能逃避你做过的事 杰森
You can't outrun what you did, Jason.
是你造就了你自己
You made yourself into who you are.
最终你必须面对现实
Eventually you're gonna have to face the fact.
你是自愿的
You volunteered.
萨曼塔斯 希腊
希腊-阿尔巴尼亚边境
瓦西里  你先上
十块钱押塞尔维亚人
二十块押塞尔维亚人
十块钱押俄国人
雷克雅未克  冰岛
克里斯蒂安·迪索特 约好的
Christian Dassault made a reservation.
用SQL注入 破坏他们的数据库
杜布纳48k
中央情报局
兰利 弗吉尼亚州
对中情局失去信心
参议院情报委员会调查中情局
运行预测算法
阿勒颇
叙利亚
希瑟·李
Heather Lee.
检测到未授权设备
长官 有一台1993年分配给俄罗斯
Ma'am, we have a device issued to a stay-behind team
新西伯利亚待命队伍的机器
in Novosibirsk, Russia, in 1993.
库存清单上的状态为已损坏
Marked on our inventory as destroyed.
它正在对我们进行正面攻击
It's knocking on our front door.
秘密行动
复制到USB设备
正在把"秘密行动"文件夹下载到USB设备中
什么情况
What's the status?
那个人什么也没干
Whoever it is, is just sitting there idle.
没有外出流量 什么都没干
There's no outbound traffic, nothing.
杜布纳48k  中情局主服务器728/96
让开
Move.
系统缺口
他们找到了一处后门
They've found a back door.
我们需要远程命令环境 我去定位来源
We need the reverse shell. I'm gonna locate the source.
我来弄
I'm working on it.
各位 我们的保密主机受到重大入侵
Okay, people, we have a major breach of our classified mainframe.
放下手头的一切 都去忙这件事
Drop everything you're doing, get on it right now!
韦伯·理查德
分析师
大卫·韦伯(儿子)
踏脚石行动
韦伯 大卫
长官 我这就把命令环境发给你
Ma'am, I'm sending you the shell.
收到
Got it.
- 现在就要 - 对
- Need it right now? - Yeah.
- 查找IP地址 - 路由跟踪呢
- Getting IP. - Where's that traceroute?
不明用户 正在监视
Unknown user. Monitoring.
雷克雅未克
IP追踪终端
Reykjavik.
秘密行动黑客大本营
SecOps hacking camp.
切断那栋楼的电源
Kill the power to the building.
马上进入那里的电网系统
Get into that power grid now.
遵命
Yes, sir.
启动植入程序
远程病毒程序激活
检测到外部追踪
- 我控制了那栋楼的电力 - 待命
- I've got the power to the building. - Stand by.
- 十秒 - 我们首先解决这件事
- Ten seconds. - Let's get on top of this.
病毒程序植入成功
- 切断电力 - 收到 切断电力
- Shut it down. - Copy that. Shutting it down.
你还能联网吗？
麦克利恩  弗吉尼亚州
仅限中情局局长阅
杜威
Dewey.
我们被黑了
We've just been hacked.
有多严重
How badly?
可能比斯诺登事件更严重
Could be worse than Snowden.
知道是谁干的吗
Is there any attribution?
我们正在调查
We're working on it.
李说肯定是非常了解我们系统的人
Lee says it must be someone with a deep knowledge of our systems.
可能会影响到 深梦和铁手行动
This could affect Deep Dream, and Iron Hand.
一小时后在会议室给我报告
I want a briefing in my conference room in one hour.
深梦公司
硅谷 加利福尼亚州
对
Yes.
- 确认了吗？- 是的 确实有入侵
- Did you get confirmation? - Yeah, there was a hack.
我们暴露了吗
So are we exposed?
还不清楚 我们还在查
We don't know yet. We're checking.
给杜威打电话 安排在华盛顿见一次面
I want you to call Dewey. Set up a meet in DC.
亚伦 现在是关键时刻
Aaron, we got a lot at stake here,
- 我们不该再找麻烦了 - 去照做吧
- maybe we shouldn't rock the boat. - Just do it.
乔治 准备好发布了吗
Hey, George. We ready for the launch?
情报库
杜布纳48k 序列号 KO35M9214
已标记为  已知设备
查看近期活动
最近活动  按日期排序
克里斯蒂安·迪索特
女性  三十岁出头
女性 30-35岁 冰岛 港口机场
305项匹配结果
匹配
尼基·帕森斯 踏脚石行动
与杰森·伯恩有关联
希瑟 你认识国家情报局局长吧
Heather, you know the Director of National Intelligence?
希瑟·李 网络部 长官
Heather Lee, Cyber Ops, sir.
知道是谁吗
Have you got a name for us?
黑客是前中情局特工
The hacker was a former Agency operative.
可能与 克里斯蒂安·迪索特合作
Believed to be working with Christian Dassault,
曾与杰森·伯恩有关联
and previously linked to Jason Bourne.
伯恩
Bourne?
- 天啊 - 他们拿到了什么
- Jesus Christ. - What did they get?
秘密行动文件
Black-ops files.
从踏脚石行动到铁手行动
From Treadstone all the way to Iron Hand.
铁手行动
Iron Hand?
但它还未实施呢 天啊
But that's not even operational yet, for Christ's sakes.
尼基·帕森斯 现在在哪儿？
Where is Nicky Parsons right now?
在路上
On the move.
她离开了雷克雅未克 经布加勒斯特到雅典
She left Reykjavik, traveling through Bucharest to Athens.
我觉得她是要去见什么人
Feels like a meet to me.
你们准备怎么处理
Well, how are you going to handle it?
彻底解决此事
We cut the head off this thing.
长官 我想指挥这次行动
Sir, I'd like to be point on this operation.
你没受过这方面的训练
You're not indoctrinated for this material.
我已经参与进来了
I'm already into it.
我在帕森斯下载的文档中 植入了病毒软件
I embedded malware into Parsons' download.
一旦有人打开这些文件 我就能跟踪到
When those files are opened, I can trace them.
让我加入吧
Let me in.
我会把帕森斯和文件交给你们的
I'll deliver Parsons, the files,
如果伯恩出现 我也会抓到他
and, if he's out there, I'll give you Bourne, too.
失陪了
Excuse me.
我欣赏你的热情
I appreciate your enthusiasm,
但不要把你的个人计划 强推给国家情报局局长
but do not push your personal agenda to the DNI again.
明白
Understood.
好了 你应该能帮上忙
All right. I think you can help me.
本次行动 我让你全权指挥
I'm going to give you full operational control on this,
保证你能调用
and I will make sure you have access to
相关人员和资源
any relevant teams and resources.
你每一步行动都要向我报告
And I want to know every move you make.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
非常感谢 长官
Thank you very much, sir.
罗马  意大利
怎么了
Yeah?
我现在需要你帮忙
I need your help, now.
我这边还没完事呢
I'm not finished here.
杰森·伯恩出现了
Jason Bourne is in play.
- 在哪儿 - 雅典
- Where? - Athens.
快把罗马的事解决掉
Close your account in Rome.
明白
Understood.
雅典  希腊
护照
美利坚合众国
伯恩
杰森
一小时后  宪法广场售货亭见
李通过视频监控查到了线索
Lee got a hit from a CCTV feed.
半小时前 帕森斯坐上一辆开往雅典西部的公交车
Parsons boarded a bus a half-hour ago, headed west across Athens.
两个小组已经在路上了
I got two local teams en route.
- 找到伯恩了吗 - 还没
- Any sign of Bourne? - Not so far.
我能感觉到 他跟这件事有关
He's involved in this somehow. I can feel it.
上传雅典所有的视频信号
Upload all Athens data and feeds,
激活实时处理程序
and activate real-time processing.
明白
Copy that.
进展如何
Where are we?
帕森斯坐的公交车 刚到宪法广场
Parsons' bus has just arrived at Syntagma Square.
希腊议会前面
There's a demonstration
有游行示威活动
in front of the Greek parliament building.
我认为 她是想用游行作掩护
I think she'll use it as cover.
派AB两组去广场
Deploy Alpha and Bravo to the square.
在议会外面的人群中
Recon for Parsons in the crowd outside parliament,
以及任何可能的汇合点 寻找帕森斯
and any possible rendezvous points.
明白 长官
Copy that, sir.
长官 特工已到位
Sir, the Asset has landed.
A组到达
Alpha Team arriving now.
收到
Copy that.
有A组的视频信号了
I have the Alpha Team feeds.
投到大屏幕上
Pull them up.
雅典警方报告称
Athens police are reporting
战术特警正朝游行人群前进
tactical teams moving on the demonstrators.
把从广场收发的社交网络信息挑出来
Isolate all social-media posts from the square.
是 长官
Yes, ma'am.
回放A1号视频
Rewind Alpha One's feed.
- 是 长官 - 二十秒
- Yes, ma'am. - Twenty seconds.
好 B2 B4 正在进入
All right, Bravo Two, Four, moving in.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我黑进了中情局
I hacked the Agency.
为了克里斯蒂安·迪索特
For Christian Dassault.
我拿到了所有的秘密行动文件
I got all the black-ops files.
我们要在网上公开它们
We're putting them online.
我们得走了
We need to move.
停
Stop.
往前2秒
Two seconds forward.
金发
Blonde hair.
画质增强
Enhance.
找到她了
Find her.
在宪法广场发现 尼基·帕森斯
Nicky Parsons sighted in Syntagma Square.
重定向至斯塔迪奥街南
Redirect south on Stadiou.
我说过 克里斯蒂安·迪索特会害死你的
I told you, Christian Dassault is going to get you killed.
我们别无选择 杰森
We don't have a choice, Jason.
一个新的计划 又开始了
It's started again. A new program.
铁手行动 比以往的更糟糕
Iron Hand. It's even worse than before.
那跟我有什么关系
What's that got to do with me?
因为它重要 真的重要
Because it matters. It matters.
对我来说 不重要
Not to me, it doesn't.
唯一重要的是活着
All that matters is staying alive.
销声匿迹 活下来
You get off the grid, survive.
我不信 你也不信
I don't believe that and neither do you.
看看你自己
Look at yourself.
看看你在干什么
Look at what you're doing.
你不能再这样下去了
You can't live like this for much longer.
杰森 我来是因为我发现了些东西
Jason, I came here because I found something.
我在踏脚石行动的文件中 发现了你父亲的名字
I found your father's name in the Treadstone files.
他是个分析师
He was an analyst.
他没参与行动 他离行动远得很
He wasn't in Operations. He wasn't near any of that stuff.
我告诉你 我看见了什么
I'm telling you what I saw.
看起来他直接参与了行动
It looked like he was involved directly.
不止如此
And there's more.
关于你 还不止如此
More about you.
什么意思
What do you mean?
早在你加入行动之前 他们就在监视你
Before you joined the program, they were watching you.
监视我
Watching me?
你折磨自己太久了 杰森
You've tortured yourself for a long time now, Jason.
你为自己的行为而折磨自己
You torture yourself for what you've done.
但你不知道 他们对你那么做的真相
But you don't know the truth about what they did to you.
你得看看那些文件
You need to read those files.
快走 他们追踪了你
Move. They tracked you.
A1看见两个目标 一男一女
Alpha One has eyes on two targets. One female, one male.
确认男性的身份
Identify the male.
收到 长官
Copy that, sir.
A1 我们要确认男性目标的身份
Alpha One, we need an ID on the male target.
趁警察还没封锁这一区域
We've got to get out of here
我们得离开这里
before the police cut off this part of the city.
往北走
Head north.
在雅典娜神像那儿汇合
Meet me at the statue of Athena.
我来对付他们
I'll take them with me.
是他
That's him.
快走
Now.
跟紧伯恩
Stay with Bourne.
可以交手
Clear to engage the target.
明白
Copy.
A组跟紧那名男子 可以交手
Alpha Team, stay with the male. You are clear to engage.
走
Come on.
长官 A组失联了
Sir, Alpha Team comms are down.
我们跟丢了 他把他们干掉了
We've lost him, sir. He's taken them out.
找到帕森斯 他会回去找她的
Find Parsons. He'll come back to get her.
长官 暴乱在蔓延
Sir, rioting is spreading.
希腊政府宣布进入紧急状态
The Greek government is declaring a state of emergency.
B组 重新锁定帕森斯
Bravo Team, we are retargeting Parsons.
找到她了
We got her.
分头行动 包围她
Split the team, put her in a box.
一名符合伯恩特征的疑犯
A suspect matching Bourne's description
偷了警方的摩托车
has stolen a police motorcycle.
他去找帕森斯了
He's coming for Parsons.
特工怎么还没到
Where the hell is the Asset?
还有两分钟 长官
Two minutes out, sir.
帕森斯在雅典娜神像附近
Parsons is at the statue of Athena.
明白
Copy that.
B组失联
Bravo Team is down.
长官 特工马上到达
Sir, the Asset is arriving on scene.
- 把行车记录仪的画面调出来 - 明白
- Pull up the dash cam. - Copy.
给我视频信号 我要能直接和特工联系
Give me the feed and direct comms to the Asset.
接近目标
Engaging targets.
我在访问雅典警方的战术数据
I'm accessing Athens police tactical data.
我需要空中视角
I need eyes overhead.
调用卫星
Bring up the satellite suite.
长官 有一颗米斯蒂和KH-12卫星可用
Sir, I'm showing a Misty and a KH-12 satellite available.
- 用KH-12 - 遵命
- Light up the 12. - Yes, sir.
卫星视频信号上线
Satellite video feed is online.
检测到路障 目标 特工
警方封锁了往北走的路
Police have blocked the road to the north.
目标会被迫左转
The target will be forced to turn left.
两百米后有另一处路障
Another barricade in 200 meters.
目标再次左转
Target turning left again.
伯恩会前往小巷
Bourne's heading for the alley.
山顶左边
Left at the top of the hill.
有楼梯
Stairway.
上山 往东走
Up the hill. Heading east.
给我一处攻击点
Give me a strike point
他找到出路了
He's found a way out.
你左边两百米
Two hundred meters to your left.
索勒姆街19号 上屋顶
19 Solomou. Get to the roof.
目标会在你视线内经过
Target should pass within your line of sight.
索勒姆街19号 明白
19 Solomou. Copy.
卫星锁定这些坐标
Focus the satellites on these coordinates.
摩托车出现时 即刻锁定
And give me a lock on the motorcycle when it gets there.
明白
Copy that.
我看到目标了 他们走蛇街到和谐广场
I've got the targets. They're approaching Omonia from Fidiou.
往西边看
Look west.
长街
The long boulevard.
目标将在55秒后到达你的位置
Coming at you in 55 seconds.
明白
Copy that.
特工上线
The Asset is online.
目标15秒后到达
Target"s with you in 15 seconds
5秒
Five seconds.
到了
Contact.
趴下
Stay low!
找机会开枪
Find a shot.
抓好了
Hold on!
目标停止活动
Targets are down.
伯恩在哪儿
Where's Bourne?
长官 警方直升机
Ma'am, a police helicopter
在楼顶特工旁边发现三具尸体
spotted three bodies on the roof near the Asset.
战术特警马上就到
A tactical team's on its way.
尼基
Nicky?
别动
Don't move!
雅典警方已进入大楼
Athens police have entered the building.
特工 你得马上离开
Asset, you need to get out of there.
不
Negative.
我们还不知道伯恩的生死
We don't even know if Bourne's alive.
你想失去他吗
You want to lose this guy?
我是杜威局长
This is Director Dewey.
给你二十秒
You have 20 seconds.
坚持住 尼基
Hold on, Nicky.
我这就带你到安全的地方
I'm going to get you to cover.
不
No.
No, don't.
我这就过去
I'm coming.
- 找出克里斯蒂安·迪索特 - 是 长官
- Get a location on Christian Dassault. - Yes, sir.
如果他和尼基·帕森斯合作
If he was working with Nicky Parsons,
就能带我们找到杰森·伯恩
he will lead us to Jason Bourne.
要是植入的病毒软件有线索 就告诉我
And let me know if you get a hit on that malware.
长官 我想弄清楚一件事
Sir, can I clarify one thing?
说吧
Yeah.
特工认识伯恩吗
Does the Asset know Bourne?
为什么这么问
Why would you ask me that?
他在楼顶的行为
His behavior on the rooftop.
说明他们有联系
It suggested a connection.
伯恩最后一次回来时
The last time Bourne came back,
揭发了黑烟斗行动
he exposed the Blackbriar program.
暴露了进行中的行动
It compromised active operations.
该特工当时在叙利亚卧底
The Asset was in Syria undercover.
他被捕 受折磨
He was captured, tortured,
我们花了两年时间才救出他
and it took two damn years to get him out.
所以你认为那是伯恩想要文件的原因
So you think that's why Bourne wants the files?
他想再曝光一次
To go public again?
我不知道他为什么回来
I have no idea why he came back.
但他肯定想毁掉我们
But whatever he's doing, he wants to destroy us.
不能让这种事发生
We can't let that happen.
你一有消息就给我打电话
So, you give me a call soon as you hear anything.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
已加密
铁手
踏脚石
与理查德·韦伯有关
杰森·伯恩受到监视
迪索特
柏林
科维兹广场  柏林
现在 有请深梦的创始人和董事长
And now, the founder and chairman of Deep Dream,
亚伦·卡鲁尔
Aaron Kalloor.
大家都知道 我为何而来
You all know why we're here.
我们要推出一款新平台
We're gonna be unveiling a new platform.
它是我们勇敢迈出的新一步
We think it is a bold new step
能让我们更好地服务社会
to allow us to serve our community better.
我们目前的社会
We're a community right now
超越了国家边界
that is transcending national boundaries.
我们有十五亿用户
And I think we're 1.5 billion users.
简而言之 我们现在的生态系统
In a nutshell, as you know, we have an ecosystem
有成千上万个应用
of hundreds of thousands of apps at this point.
新平台的功能
And what this new platform will do
就是整合用户的数据和偏好
will be to integrate users' data and preferences,
利用这些信息
and use that information
来丰富并量身定制每位用户的体验
to enrich and tailor-make each unique user experience
这一方法前所未有
in a way that is, frankly, unprecedented.
我看见 有些记者在奋笔疾书
Um, now, I can see some journalists' pens twitching,
- 准备提问隐私问题 - 对
- ready to ask about privacy. - Yeah.
许多人都担心这一问题 理应如此
This is a concern to many people, and so it should be.
因为隐私对我们来说真的太重要了
I mean, this is something that matters to us.
我想说
And let me just say, uh,
我理解没人想被监视
I understand nobody wants to feel like they're being watched.
我可以这么说
So let me just tell you,
你来到深梦 选择了我们提供的服务
when you come to Deep Dream, when you use our service,
没人会监视你
no one will be watching you.
- 卡鲁尔先生 - 这边请 先生
- Mr. Kalloor. - Right this way, sir.
祝用餐愉快
Enjoy your meal.
谢谢
Thank you.
恭喜
Congratulations.
听说股东对新平台很满意
I hear your stockholders were very happy with that new platform.
听说你被入侵了
And I heard you got hacked.
我们正在处理
We're dealing with it.
这影响很大 太冒险了
This changes everything. There's too much risk.
我不干了
I'm out.
亚伦
Aaron,
你极有天赋 洞察力也很强
you are an extraordinarily gifted and perceptive young man.
你答应帮我们的时候
When you agreed to help us,
是因为你知道有多大的威胁…
it was because you understood the very grave threats that...
你知道 如果这一协议被公开
Do you have any idea of the shit-storm I'll have on my hands
我将面临什么吗
if this arrangement becomes public?
斯诺登事件 对我的打击已经够大了
I already took a hit with Snowden,
你还想再来一次
and you want more?
我们的敌人变得更狡猾了
Our enemies have become much more sophisticated.
只收集大数据已经不够了
Gathering metadata is no longer adequate.
我们需要后门来进入你的平台
We need a back door into your new platform,
一条能绕开加密体系的捷径
and a way past the encryptions.
如果还不够 你还会提新的要求
And when that's not enough, you'll want something new.
你不明白 是不是
You don't get it, do you?
隐私就是自由
Privacy is freedom.
也许你该考虑保护它
Maybe that's something you should think about defending.
你个混蛋
You little prick,
你的公司刚起步时
you didn't believe in privacy or freedom
你可没想什么隐私和自由
when we funded your startup,
是我们的资助 让你成为亿万富翁
turned you into a billionaire.
我已经还给你了 翻了很多倍
I paid you back many, many, many times over.
我一直很不愿意
And I was never comfortable with any of this.
我不干了
I'm out.
我不想再出卖用户了
I'm done selling out our customers.
可你却愿意出卖国家
But you would sell out your country.
说实话 要不是你感到有风险
The truth is, we wouldn't be having this conversation
也不会来跟我见面
if you didn't feel personally at risk.
你口口声声说什么自由的因特网
You talk about a free Internet,
什么自己在拯救世界
you tell yourself you're saving the world,
其实你只是让世界变得更危险
but all you're doing is making it a much more dangerous place.
当然了 你也让保卫国家的工作
And you're sure as hell making
越来越艰难了
this country much more difficult to defend.
这些当然都要算到你头上 亚伦
And you're sure as hell accountable for that, Aaron.
都算到你头上
Accountable.
柏林  德国
阿尔伯特·赫奇医生
踏脚石计划
特工行为分析
杰森·伯恩
行为模式评估
伯恩离开计划时
遗忘了自己身份的关键信息
实际上 他失去了自己存在的理由
根据我的评估 伯恩在社会上永远无法安宁
总有一天会越界
这时 如果手段得当 可以使伯恩重返计划
伯恩
Bourne?
所有东西都放到桌上
Everything on the table.
打开
Open it.
好
Sure.
伯恩露面了 在柏林
Bourne has surfaced. In Berlin.
叫柏林的小组行动
Get the Berlin team up.
她在哪
Where is she?
她死了
She's dead.
她知道有风险
She knew the risks.
我警告过她
I warned her.
她自己做了选择
She made a choice.
你利用了她
You exploited her.
柏林的小组出发了
Berlin team is mobile.
在什么位置
What do we have on the location?
地址跟克里斯蒂安·迪索特有关
It's an address linked to Christian Dassault.
伯恩呢
Anything on Bourne?
没消息 我在连接视频监控
Nothing yet. I'm accessing CCTV now.
长官 我在想 我们是不是弄错了
Sir, I've been thinking, maybe we've got this wrong.
如果他不是冲着我们呢
What if he's not coming for us?
如果是其他事呢
What if it's something else?
你根本不知道他是什么人
You don't have any idea who you're dealing with.
我们应该合作 伯恩
We should work together, Bourne.
你暴露了黑烟斗项目
You exposed the Blackbriar program.
我们的目标一致 不是吗
We're both after the same thing, right?
我们都想扳倒
We both want to take down
控制社会的腐败机构
the corrupt institutions that control society.
我跟你不是一边的
I'm not on your side.
已连入视频监控系统
CCTV feed is online.
他在用电脑
He's on a computer.
我们得阻止他
We have to stop this.
如果文件到了网上 行动就暴露了
If he puts those files online, operations will be compromised
会死人的
and people will die.
好的 长官
Yes, sir.
等你完事了 好歹把文件留给我
At least when you're done, leave me the files.
这些计划都要曝光
These programs have to be exposed.
人民有权知道
People have a right to know.
踏脚石项目
应对全球针对美国威胁的提议
理查德·韦伯
得连上他的电脑
We need that computer.
屋里有部手机
There's a phone in the room.
我能通过手机删除文件
I can use it to delete the files.
招募协议
候选人须先接受观察 以判断是否适合计划
杰森·伯恩 招募历史
- 连上手机了 - 行动小组呢
- Got the phone. - Where's that team?
5分钟后到 长官
Five minutes out, sir.
来不及了 快点
We're running out of time. Get there.
韦伯加入军方三角洲特特种部队
被选中观察是否适合踏脚石项目
联络大卫·韦伯招募事宜
踏脚石监控报告
目标 大卫·韦伯
听我说 大卫
Listen to me, David.
我做了件事
I've done something.
这件事
Something...
要付出代价
that came at a cost.
有一天你会明白的
One day you'll understand why.
我得回华盛顿了
I gotta get back to Washington.
我爱你 儿子
I love you, son.
他们打起来了 长官
They're fighting, sir.
还有一道防火墙
One more firewall.
文件删除了 长官
Files deleted, sir.
打电话过去
Call in.
伯恩 我叫希瑟·李
Bourne, my name is Heather Lee.
我不是负责人
I'm not in charge here.
你失踪的时候我不在这
I wasn't here when you went missing.
我看到 你在查阅以前的踏脚石文件
I can see you're going through the old Treadstone files.
你在回溯你的过去
Retracing your history.
我知道你在寻找什么
I know you're looking for something.
让我来帮你
Let me help you find it.
把电话给我
Give me that phone.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
杰森 我是罗伯特·杜威 还记得我吗
Jason, this is Robert Dewey. Do you remember me?
杰森 你爸爸是爱国者
Jason, your dad was a patriot.
他早就知道 美国面临威胁
He could see the threats that America was facing,
像你一样 他出于巨大的使命感
and, like you, he chose to serve his country
选择了为国效命
out of a profound sense of duty.
他不会希望你破坏中情局的
He would not want to see you harm the Agency.
你得住手了
You have to stop this.
现在就得住手
And you have to stop it now.
长官 预计还有…
Sir, our ETA is...
有行动组靠近 还有两分钟
他在移动了 准备好
He's on the move. Be ready.
就位
Take point!
跟着我
On me!
电梯
The elevator.
我们跟丢了 长官
We lost him, sir.
马尔科姆·史密斯 承包商 常驻伦敦
Malcolm Smith, contract only, based out of London.
90年代招募伯恩的时候 踏脚石的监视
Ran all of Treadstone's surveillance in the late '90s,
都是他负责的
when Bourne was recruited.
他还活动吗
Is he still active?
改行做私人安保了
He's private security now.
联系特工 告诉他
Contact the Asset and tell him
六个小时内要到伦敦
I want him on the ground in London in six hours.
我认为不该这么做 长官
I think that could be a mistake, sir.
不应该 为什么
A mistake? Why?
对伯恩究竟是抓是杀 还存在争议
There is an argument for catching Bourne instead of killing him.
来说说吧
All right, let's hear it.
伯恩消失了很久
Bourne's been off the grid for a long time.
他一直藏在阴影中 他经历过很多事
He's been hiding in the shadows, he's seen things.
他知道的信息 能帮助我们
He knows things that could help us.
带他回来才是明智的
Bringing him back in is the smart move.
怎么带他回来呢
And how are we going to do that?
阿尔伯特·赫奇在伯恩逃离时做了心理评估
Albert Hirsch wrote the psychal evaluation when Bourne left the program.
他认为伯恩心里依然爱国
He concluded Bourne is still a patriot at heart,
离开计划这件事 会一直纠缠着他
and that leaving the program could come back to haunt him.
你有什么建议
And what are you suggesting?
我注意到伯恩看了这些文件
I watched Bourne with those files.
他拼命寻找过去
Desperately looking into his past.
我觉得他快到临界点了
And I think he's at a tipping point.
如果能当面跟他谈谈
If I could get face-to-face with him,
我想我可以带他回来
I think I can bring him back in.
就试一次看看
One attempt.
如果失败
And if it fails,
再由你们处置
you do what you have to.
我觉得可以 你呢 鲍伯
Well, it makes sense to me. What do you think, Bob?
让她试试吧
Let's give it a shot.
好吧 做吧
All right, do it.
要么带伯恩回来 要么就干掉
Bring Bourne in, or tie it off.
这次必须了结
But this ends now.
谢谢 长官
Thank you, sir.
长官 抱歉…
Sir, I'm sorry...
没关系
No, don't worry about that.
去睡会儿吧 孩子
Better get some sleep, kid.
你接下来的24小时 会很漫长
You got a long 24 hours ahead of you.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
拖得太久了
It's taking too long.
都快发布了 还有这么多问题
It shouldn't still be buggy this close to launch.
我觉得问题不多
Well, I don't think it's buggy.
我觉得我们做的修改
I think we've changed some things
改变了一些参数
that's going to change the parameters.
我们得去…
We're going to have to go and...
好了 得改回来
Okay, we need to change them back.
阿曼达 把修改记录交给凯尔
Amanda, can we get that note over to Kyle?
- 好的 - 我觉得你是对的
- Absolutely. - Look, I think you're right,
- 只是我们可能不… - 我等不及了
- I just don't think we want to... - I'm tired of waiting.
卡鲁尔先生
Mr. Kalloor.
这是怎么回事
What the hell is this?
卡鲁尔先生 我是约翰·布罗斯
Mr. Kalloor, my name is John Burroughs.
来自美国司法部
I'm from the Department of Justice.
我向您出示由美国政府颁发的
I'm hereby serving you with the enclosed complaint...
真的吗 非得在大庭广众之下吗
Really? We have to do this in public?
这张指控书
issued by the US government
指控深梦集团违反谢尔曼法案
against Deep Dream Corporation for violation of the Sherman Act.
该指控书要求您
This complaint requires you to
保留所有个人及公司财务记录
preserve all personal and corporate financial records
直到反托拉斯动议提交至联邦法庭
pending antitrust motions to be filed in federal court.
祝你愉快
Good day.
- 是杜威干的 - 亚伦 这是在警告我们
- This is Dewey. - Aaron, it's a message.
我们得好好考虑一下了
And maybe we should think about
趁事态还没恶化
what we're doing before it gets any worse.
你觉得满足了他 就万事大吉了吗
So, you think if we give him what he wants, it'll end there?
我只是说也许我们该倾听一下
You know, I'm just saying that maybe we should listen.
调出我跟杜威
I want you to pull up all the
所有的会面记录
records of all the meetings I've ever had with Dewey.
所有记录 私下的讨论也包括吗
All the records? Even the off-the-books discussions?
尤其是那些
Especially those.
我们去维加斯 我需要保险措施
We're going to Vegas. I need an insurance policy.
你在伦敦吗
Are you in London?
在
Yes.
为什么派她来
Why are you sending her?
她有她的用处
She serves a purpose.
我一个人行动
I work alone.
这次不行
Not this time.
别搞成私人恩怨
Don't make this personal.
伯恩背叛了我们 当然是私人恩怨
Bourne betrayed us. It's always been personal.
你知道自己面对的是谁
You know who you're dealing with.
赶快准备好
You better make sure you're ready.
深梦有些事你得知道
There's something you should know about Deep Dream.
但你得保证
But I need an assurance
你是支持我的
that I have your support.
可以 什么事
You got it. What do you have?
卡鲁尔在维加斯有计划
Kalloor is planning something for Vegas.
伦敦 英国
哪位
Yes?
我是杰森·伯恩
This is Jason Bourne.
我要跟你谈谈
I need to talk.
谈什么
What about?
我已经不为中情局工作了
I don't work for the Agency anymore.
帕丁顿广场 15分钟后
Paddington Plaza, 15 minutes.
伯恩刚给史密斯打电话了
Bourne just called Smith.
他们在帕丁顿广场见面
They're meeting at Paddington Plaza.
15分钟后
15 minutes.
我们会全程跟踪史密斯
We'll tail Smith the whole way.
看到伯恩之后 我就接近他
As soon as we get eyes on Bourne, I'll approach him.
不管做什么 尽量收敛点
Whatever you do, stay contained.
我不想惊动英国人 问东问西的
I don't want the Brits crawling all over us, asking questions.
明白
Understood.
追踪设备
Tracking device.
你守住桥的南侧
You'll hold on the south side of the bridge.
有需要我就联系你
I'll contact you if I need you.
好
Sure.
你说了算
You're the boss, right?
目标在移动 前往运河
Subject is on the move. Heading toward the canal.
A组 跟他平行前进
Alpha Team, take a parallel track.
B组 在后面跟着他
Bravo Team, follow the subject from behind.
留意伯恩
And keep your eyes open for Bourne.
B组正在跟踪
Bravo Team tailing subject.
出发
Let's go.
200米后右转
In 200 meters, make a right.
收到
Copy that.
通讯检查 第二频道 收到吗
Comms check. Second channel. Do you copy?
收到 你在哪儿
I have you. Where are you now?
朝史密斯前进
Heading towards Smith.
没看到伯恩
No sign of Bourne.
目标向东拐了 进了巷子
Subject has turned east, into an alley.
A组 巷子通向一座桥
Alpha Team, that alley leads to a footbridge,
目标会径直走向你们
which will bring him to you.
明白
Copy that.
B组失去联络
Bravo Team is down.
正在发送新路线给你
Sending you updated route now.
收到没有 史密斯
You copy that, Smith?
收到
Yes.
B组 怎么不动 什么情况
Bravo Team, why aren't you moving? What's going on?
B组 收到没
Bravo Team, do you copy?
怎么回事 希瑟 B组呢
What's happening, Heather? Where's Bravo?
B组失去联系
We're comms down on Bravo.
A组 是否看到目标
Alpha Team, do you have eyes on the subject?
能看到
We have eyes on.
A组 报告情况
Alpha Team, sit-rep.
A组 报告
Alpha Team, report.
什么情况 希瑟
What's happening, Heather?
A组没有回应
Alpha Team isn't responding.
B组呢
Bravo?
也没有
Still nothing.
两个组都失联了？别搞砸了 希瑟
You lost both teams? Get a grip on this operation, Heather.
这可是伯恩
That's Bourne.
让特工行动
Green-light the Asset.
长官 我需要更多时间
Sir, I need more time.
没时间了
We have no time.
你下不下命令？
Are you going to give that order or not?
长官 求你了
Sir, please.
你太天真了 看不清真相
You are too naive to see the truth.
根本不可能把伯恩带回来
There's no bringing in Bourne.
必须除掉他
He has to be put down,
而你很明显 没这个决断
and you obviously cannot do what has to be done.
我来接手行动指挥
I am taking operational control.
特工 可以行动了
Asset, you have a green light.
重复 可以除掉伯恩
Repeat, you have a green light on Bourne.
明白
Copy that.
马上就到
I'm on my way.
特工 你行动了吗
Asset, are you on the move?
特工 你的追踪设备显示你没在动
Asset, your tracking device says you're stationary.
你行动了吗
Are you moving?
希瑟 别说话 让他干活
Heather, stay off this channel. Let him do his job.
我们走
Left here.
- 快去帕丁顿广场 - 明白
- Get to Paddington Plaza, fast. - Copy that.
我到了
In position.
已锁定
Locked in.
怎么了
What's going on?
那是什么声音
What's that noise?
多处火警
Multiple fire alarms.
是伯恩干的
That's Bourne.
我该怎么办
What do I do?
原地不动
You stay there. You do not move.
请由最近的出口离开大楼
Leave the building by the nearest available exit.
我不能留在这里
I can't stay here.
你们保护不了我
You can't protect me.
我需要你留在原地 史密斯
I need you to stay where you are, Smith.
你还能看到他吗
You still have line of sight?
我看着呢
I'm on him.
你们要在人群之中 他在我身边时射杀他
You're gonna shoot him in a crowd when he's right next to me?
留在原地 史密斯
Stay where you are, Smith.
你知道他为什么会找来
You know why he's here.
他想要答案
He wants answers.
你已经失去控制了
You've lost this thing.
我得离开这里
I gotta get out of here.
该死
Shit!
怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
伯恩抓到史密斯了
Bourne's got Smith.
追上他们 我绕过去截住他们
Go after them. I'll come around and cut them off.
史密斯 我们知道你和伯恩在一起
Smith, we know you're with Bourne.
你得想办法告诉我们 你在哪里
You have to find a way to let us know where you are.
你为什么带我来这里
Why are you taking me in here?
他们肯定在广场附近
They've got to be near the Plaza.
天啊 伯恩
Jesus, Bourne!
混蛋
God damn it!
你要干什么 别激动
What are you doing? Take it easy.
理查德·韦伯
Richard Webb.
贝鲁特分站站长
Station Chief, Beirut.
他是我父亲 他创立了踏脚石
He was my father. He started Treadstone.
他让你监控我 为什么
He hired you to put me under surveillance. Why?
- 天啊 - 他为什么雇了你
- Jesus! - Why did he hire you?
什么都别说 史密斯
Don't say anything, Smith.
不 不
No. No.
找不到他们
There's no sign of them.
我们该怎么做
What do you want us to do?
沿着运河搜索
Work your way down the canal.
我绕过去跟你们汇合
I'll circle around and meet you there.
你跟踪我去了贝鲁特
You followed me to Beirut.
那是我最后一次见到我父亲
The last time I saw my father!
他为什么要你跟踪我
Why would he have you follow me?
这说不通 为什么
It doesn't make any sense. Why?
什么都别告诉他
Don't give him a goddamn thing.
为什么
Why?
老天 伯恩 我要掉下去了
Jesus Christ, Bourne! I'm falling!
伯恩 别这样
Bourne, please!
我听到了
I can hear them!
贝鲁特
Beirut.
我去是想告诉他 踏脚石来找我了
I went there to tell him that Treadstone had approached me.
但如果是他创立的计划 他为什么没和我提过
But if it was his program, why didn't he say anything to me?
我做了件事
I've done something.
这件事
Something...
要付出代价
that came at a cost.
他就是在那天被杀死的
That was the day he was killed.
官方说他是被恐怖分子杀死的
They said he was killed by terrorists.
但其实不是恐怖分子 对不对
He wasn't killed by terrorists, was he?
想想你家人的安全
Think about your family's safety,
史密斯 什么都别说
Smith. You keep your mouth shut.
下一枪我会打死你
The next bullet's in your head!
他为什么会被杀
Why was he killed?
为什么
Why?
他是因为你才被杀的
He was killed because of you.
你父亲 他没参与行动
Your father, he wasn't in Operations.
他不知道我们选中了你 等他发现后
He didn't know we'd chosen you. When he found out, he...
他威胁要把计划曝光
He threatened to expose the program.
他不想让你变成杀手
He didn't want you turned into a killer.
谁杀了他
Who killed him?
别说
Don't do it.
他在哪儿
Where is he?
他就要到了
He's almost there.
我们要彻底解决这件事
We're gonna stop this now.
别 求你了
No, please.
救命 快叫救护车
Somebody help! Call an ambulance!
救命
Someone help!
他从楼顶摔下去了 五楼
He went off the roof. Five floors.
他认出我了
He recognized me.
我去确认收尾
I'm going to make sure it's finished.
马上就有人来了
Help's coming now.
别起来 伙计
No, don't get up, mate.
请让开 让开
Step aside, please. Step aside.
都退后
Everybody step back.
- 让我们做事 - 退后
- Let us do our job. - Please step back.
有谁看见事情经过了吗
Did anybody see what happened?
他不见了
He's gone.
- 该死 - 我去找他
- Oh, shit. - I'm going after him.
顺着运河找
I'll work my way down the canal.
不 伦敦没你的事了
No. You're done in London.
你说什么
What are you talking about?
有其他任务
There's another play to be made.
他知道我们做了什么 他会来找我们的
Now that he knows what we did, he'll come for both of us,
那也许是办成另一件事的机会
and that could be the opportunity for something else.
这不是让你复仇的
This isn't about revenge.
这就是复仇
Yes, it is.
不是他死就是我亡
And it won't be done until one of us is dead.
去机场
Get to the airport.
铁手行动出问题了
We have a problem with Iron Hand.
明白
Copy that.
报告情况
Give me a sit-rep.
目前还没动静
We've got nothing.
继续观察
Keep looking.
开车
Drive.
情况不该成这样的
It wasn't supposed to go like this.
我只是想谈谈
I wanted to talk.
杜威去哪里了
Where's Dewey going?
他去维加斯了
He's going to Vegas to speak
去一个网络展会见亚伦·卡鲁尔
with Aaron Kalloor at a cyber convention.
中情局每年都会在那里招人
The Agency recruits there every year.
什么是铁手行动
What's Iron Hand?
杜威新创立的秘密行动计划
Dewey's new black-ops program.
全方位监控
Full-spectrum surveillance.
随时随地监控每一个人
Watching everyone all the time.
杜威需要卡鲁尔的合作 才能上线运行
Dewey needs Kalloor's cooperation to bring it online.
我要下车
Let me out.
我可以帮你过去
I can help you get there.
你为什么要这么做
Why would you do that?
你我虽然理由不同 但都是要除掉杜威
You and I have different reasons, but we both want Dewey gone.
给 拿着
Here, take this.
维加斯见
I'll see you in Vegas.
长官
Sir.
我们准备将卡鲁尔遇刺一事
We're pinning Kalloor's hit
嫁祸给一个虚构的圣战分子
on a fictional jihadi shooter.
一个20岁的伊拉克人
A 20-year-old Iraqi national.
我们伪造了银行账户
We created bank accounts,
旅行文件 电子邮件和电话记录
travel documents, e-mails, phone records.
让他看起来像是单干的
He'll look like a lone wolf.
有实际证据吗
Any physical evidence?
特工会留下枪 枪上会有伊拉克人的指纹
The Asset leaves the gun. It'll have the Iraqi's prints on it.
这件事不需要让拉塞尔知道
Russell doesn't need to know about this.
我明白 长官
I understand, sir.
有伯恩的消息吗
Any news on Bourne?
没有
Nothing.
他一定会来找我的
He was always gonna come for me.
如果他来了 我们会处理的
Well, if it happens, we'll deal with it.
你为什么去伦敦 迈克尔斯先生
What was the purpose of your visit to London, Mr. Michaels?
商务访问
Business.
欢迎回家 先生
Welcome home, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
停车场安全 可以进去了
Parking lot clear. You're good to go.
长官 楼上已经安排好了房间
Sir, we have a secure room for you, right upstairs.
- 祝您入住愉快 - 谢谢
- Enjoy your stay. - Thank you.
欢迎入住阿丽雅酒店
Hi, welcome to the Aria.
- 希瑟·李 开个房间 - 好的
- Heather Lee, checking in. - Okay.
未知号码
北部电梯 10分钟后
给您安排了天空套房 房间号2016
We have you in a lovely Sky Suite. Number 2016.
祝您入住愉快
Enjoy your stay.
谢谢
Thank you.
EXOCON大会2016
中情局局长罗伯特·杜威
深梦创始人及首席执行官
亚伦·卡鲁尔
亚伦
Aaron!
加油 亚伦
All right, Aaron!
深梦
Deep Dream!
联系李
Find Lee.
告诉她 我上台前要见她
Tell her I want to see her before we go on stage.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
在后台和观众席都要安排特工
I want agents posted backstage as well as the auditorium.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
让一让 让让
Coming through, make a hole.
让让 让让
Make a hole, make a hole.
这里停一下
Gonna make a quick stop here.
你们好 我是亚伦
Hey, guys. Hi. How's it going? Aaron.
很高兴见到你
Good to meet you.
可以给我一个吗
Can I get one?
谢谢你们的辛勤工作
Thanks very much for your hard work.
谢谢
Thank you.
你们干得很棒
You're doing a great job.
杰弗斯
局长要见你
是我
Yeah.
你准备好了吗
You all set?
正在查看撤离路线
Checking the departure route now.
你的时间不多
You won't have much time.
他们不知道我在哪里 时间足够
They won't know where it came from. I'll have enough time.
解决掉卡鲁尔之后
After you take care of Kalloor,
我会站在旁边 往我的左手
I'll be standing, left hand at my side.
你打上一枪
You put a bullet in it.
我也是目标会比较好
It's better if I'm a target, too.
明白
Copy that.
李
Lee.
局长上台前要见你
The Director wants a word before you go on stage.
没问题
Of course.
追踪中
证件
ID?
谢谢
Thanks.
未知号码
左口袋有东西给杜威
希瑟
Heather.
我的门生 最坚定的支持者
My protégé. Strongest supporter.
知道吗 伦敦那事之后
You know, after what happened in London,
我不知道该怎么处置你
I did not know what to do with you.
我想就把它当成是 你学习的过程吧
I suppose we'll just, um, write it off to your learning curve.
谢谢
I'd appreciate that.
至少你现在知道 你其实一点机会都没有
At least you can now see that you never had a chance.
等伯恩再次出现 由我来解决他
When Bourne turns up again, I'll deal with him.
明白吗
Do you understand?
当然
Of course.
我完全同意
I agree completely.
我们上台之后
When we get on stage,
政策问题我来回答
I'll handle all the policy questions,
技术问题你来回答
throw everything technical to you.
没问题 长官
I'll be ready, sir.
好 我们走
Okay, let's do this.
有徽章吗
Badges?
亚伦
Aaron.
罗伯特
Robert.
你认识希瑟·李吧
You know Heather Lee.
当然 我们在斯坦福是同学
Yeah, we went to Stanford together.
你在中情局感觉如何
Wow. How are you enjoying life at the Agency?
很有挑战 也很充实
Challenging. But fulfilling.
在那里还能坚守原则吗
It's tough to stay true to your principles over there?
当然 谢谢关心
My principles are just fine, thanks.
先生们 准备好了 请跟我来
Gentlemen, we're ready for you. Follow me, please.
我会享受舞台的
I'm going to enjoy this.
我也是
So am I.
谢谢 先生
Thank you, sir.
大家晚上好
Oh! Hi! How's everybody doing tonight?
欢迎
Welcome.
欢迎来到今晚的EXOCON研讨会
Welcome to tonight's EXOCON Symposium.
今天我们有幸 请来了四位尊贵的客人
We are so lucky to have four fantastic guests this evening.
中情局局长 罗伯特·杜威
The CIA Director, Robert Dewey, is here.
以及我的好朋友 EXOCON的老朋友
And a dear friend of mine, and an old friend of EXOCON,
社交媒体巨头 深梦的首席执行官亚伦·卡鲁尔
the CEO of social-media giant Deep Dream, Aaron Kalloor is here.
今晚 自由因特网的监管
Tonight, "Policing a free Internet,
个人权利和公共安全
"Personal rights versus public safety."
这是我们的时代面临的严峻问题
This is the great question of our time.
而我们的决定也影响着我们的未来
And the choices we make about this will determine our future.
让我们开始吧
So let's just dive right in, okay?
上来吧 伙计们
Come on out here, guys.
长官 有一条信息
Sir, you've got an incoming message.
优先级很高
High priority.
好吧 我得先处理这事
All right, guys, I'm gonna have to take this.
我迟点上去
I'll catch up with you later.
你们先请
Go ahead.
谢谢你们的邀请
Thanks for having me.
似乎杜威局长临时有事
It appears Director Dewey is held up momentarily,
应该不会耽搁太久
and I am being told that it shouldn't be too much longer.
但是今晚 我们会有许多安排
But we have a ton of stuff to get into tonight,
所以我们可以先行
so we can start anyway...
布拉德 布拉德 我可以说两句吗
Brad? Brad, could I say a few words?
- 你说什么 - 我可以说两句吗
- Excuse me? - Can I get the ball rolling?
当然了 女士们先生们 亚伦·卡鲁尔
Oh, sure, man, by all means. Ladies and gentlemen, Aaron Kalloor.
谢谢 非常感谢
Thank you. Thanks a lot.
非常感谢 布拉德和EXOCON的伙计们
Thanks a lot to Brad and all the folks at EXOCON
再次邀请我们 也谢谢你们能前来
for having us back, and to you guys for turning out.
在局长来之前
Before the Director comes out to join us,
我想能先和你们聊几句
I just wanted to share a few words with you guys.
很久之前 我有个想法
A long time ago, I had this idea.
- 收到 - 美好的想法 创造一个空间
- Copy that. - A beautiful idea, to create a place, online...
面部识别有结果了
Facial recognition got a hit.
伯恩乘英国航空公司的飞机 从希斯罗机场出发
Bourne was on a BA flight from Heathrow to Vegas.
两小时前抵达了维加斯
It landed two hours ago.
他怎么通过入境检查的
How the hell did he get through immigration?
有人给他的护照 授予了中情局安全权限
Someone issued him an Agency security clearance on his passport.
结果是一个非常受欢迎的想法
Well, it turned out to be a pretty popular idea.
全世界的人们 开始使用我们的服务
People from around the world started using our service.
未知号码
出事了
首先 这让我
Well, first off, this has all
富有 但不健康
made me a lot more rich than is probably healthy.
我上台之后 解决卡鲁尔和那个女孩
When I come on stage, take care of Kalloor and the girl.
收到
Copy.
但是我要说的是
But, what I mean to say is that, you know,
成功有其代价
all this success has come at a cost.
深梦的核心得了绝症
There is a cancer at the heart of Deep Dream.
一个让我非常内疚的秘密
A guilty secret, and, um...
我必须告诉你们所有人
I have to share it with all of you guys.
这个混蛋要搞垮我们
Son of a bitch is about to take us down.
立刻解决卡鲁尔和那个女孩
Take out Kalloor and the girl right now.
- 别动 - 好的
- Stay there. - Okay.
在我创业初期
When I was starting out, I, uh...
为了让公司起步 我收了钱
I took money to start my company.
和魔鬼做了交易
Made a bargain with a guy in a dark suit...
他现在想要拿走我的灵魂
and now he's come back to take my soul.
枪手在那里
I see the shooter!
看到杰森·伯恩了
We've got eyes on Jason Bourne.
他还活着 叫救护车
He's still breathing. Call an ambulance!
走 走
Go, go!
- 我们走 - 长官 我们得走了
- Let's go! - Sir, we gotta go.
去出口
Head for the exit!
我是瓦斯科斯 我们看到伯恩了
This is Vasquez. We're on Bourne.
去把车准备好
Get the cars ready!
快去把车准备好
Get the cars ready right now!
送我回房间
No, take me to the suite.
长官 我们得带你离开 伯恩在这里
Sir, we've got to get you out of here. Bourne is on the loose.
你听到了 送我回房间
You heard me. Take me to the suite.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
送他回房间 送他上楼
Take him to the suite. Take him upstairs.
送他上楼
Get him upstairs.
赶快 赶快
Right now. Right now.
上楼去房间
Up to the suite.
- 我们走 快 - 是 长官
- Let's go, right now. Go, go, go! - Yes, sir.
这边走 这边走 别紧张 这里
Come this way. This way. Don't worry. Come on.
别挡路 联邦探员
Out of the way! Federal agent!
瓦斯科斯 报告情况
Vasquez, sit-rep.
瓦斯科斯 回话
Vasquez, come in!
找到他了 长官 我是科里尔
Okay, we've got him. Sir, this is Collier.
- 我们找到狙击手了 - 该死
- We've ID'd the sniper. - Shit.
我们在分发他的照片
We're circulating his photo now.
伯恩呢
What about Bourne?
等等
Hang on.
伯恩刚刚离开
Okay, Bourne is just leaving
西边的应急通道 往大堂去了
the west service corridor, heading for the lobby.
明白 盯住伯恩
Copy that. Stay on Bourne.
怎么了
What?
我们还在寻找伯恩 他们发现特工了
We're still looking for Bourne. And they've ID'd the Asset.
回一楼去 等候进一步通知
Go back to the first floor and wait for further instructions.
- 是 长官 明白 - 明白
- Yes, sir. Copy that. - Copy that.
都趴下 快趴下
Everybody down! Right now!
趴下 让开 让开 让开
Down, move, move, move!
别挡路 联邦特工 让开
Out of the way! Federal agents! Move!
带一队人从东北部的电梯上去 到楼上汇合
Take a team to the northeast elevators. I'll meet you up there.
伯恩上去找你了
Bourne's on his way up to you.
你来的时间有点长 杰森
You took a long time to get here, Jason.
我知道贝鲁特的事了
I know about Beirut.
我知道你们干了什么
I know what you did.
今晚一切都将结束
It all ends tonight.
直接动手会更简单
Be a lot easier to do it right away.
你来不是为了复仇的
You didn't come here for revenge.
你来是因为你知道 该回来了
You came here because you know it's time to come in.
你父亲创立了这个计划
Your father created the program.
却没本事完成这个计划
Didn't have what it takes to make it work.
但你有
And you did.
你一直都有
You always did.
所以你才会自愿报名
That's why you volunteered.
那是因为我以为 他是被我们的敌人杀死的
I volunteered because I thought our enemies killed him.
我因为一个谎言而自愿报名
I volunteered because of a lie.
不 你自愿报名是出于你的自我
No, you volunteered because of who you are.
因为你就是杰森·伯恩
You volunteered because you are Jason Bourne,
而不是大卫·韦伯
and not David Webb.
杀了三十二个人 杰森
Thirty-two kills, Jason.
每杀死一个人 都让这个世界改变
Every one of them made a difference.
这个国家的国民 因为你而更加安全
People all across this country are safer because of what you did.
我在寻找另一种方式
I'm trying to find another way.
那你找到了吗
And how's that working out for you?
你永远都无法找到内心的平静
You're never going to find any peace.
直到你承认自己究竟是谁
Not until you admit to yourself who you really are.
是时候回来了 杰森
It's time to come in, Jason.
你该回来了
It's time to come in.
我不能
I can't.
至少不能为了你
Not for you.
你没来过这里
You were never here.
你不用去找他
You don't have to go after him.
现在就可以结束
This can stop now.
你可以做出选择
You have a choice.
- 快走 - 请拿出你们的身份证件
- Let's go! - Have your IDs ready.
拿出你们的身份证件 先生们女士们
Have your IDs ready, ladies and gentlemen.
拿出你们的身份证件 这边 快走
Have your IDs ready! Come on, guys, let's go, let's go!
排队走 拉斯维加斯警察 女士们先生们
Stand in a line. Las Vegas Police, ladies and gentlemen!
一辆特警装甲车和无牌黑色道奇冲锋者
BearCat SWAT truck and unmarked black Dodge Charger
在阿丽雅酒店门口被盗
stolen from the front of the Aria.
正在追踪 请求空中支援
Pursuit in progress. Air support requested.
是什么人
What was that ID?
拦下他 把路口堵起来
Stop him! Block that road!
上帝啊
Oh, my God!
开火
Fire!
跟上
Move out!
让开
Move!
两个单位追踪中 请确认
Next two units involved, identify.
这里是空中1号 请注意 疑犯车辆
This is Air 1. Be advised, suspect vehicles
撞进了里维埃拉酒店东南入口
have crashed into the southeast entrance of the Riviera.
一名武装疑犯
We have an armed suspect
正在走进里维埃拉酒店南边的雨水管道
heading into the storm drain south of the Riviera.
你是个叛徒 一直都是个叛徒
You're a traitor. You've always been a traitor.
骨子里就是
It's in your blood.
卡鲁尔先生
Mr. Kalloor!
亚伦 你在大会上想跟大家说的是什么
Aaron! What were you going to tell everyone at the convention?
你在隐瞒些什么 亚伦
What are you hiding, Aaron?
为什么有人会想暗杀你
Why did somebody try to assassinate you?
深梦核心的绝症究竟是什么
What's the cancer at the heart of Deep Dream?
我认为在这个时候
I think it would be
做出任何评论都很不合适
inappropriate to pass any comment at this stage,
但我很期待和当局合作
but I look forward to working with the authorities
查明谁敢对此事负责
to find out who was responsible.
至于深梦
And to getting back to Deep Dream,
我们将继续我们重要的工作 谢谢
where we can continue our important work. Thank you.
你有没有欺骗你的用户
Have you been lying to your users?
先生
Sir.
我想说我很抱歉 先生
I wanted to say I'm sorry, sir.
关于维加斯的事
About Vegas.
杜威局长的做法并不明智
Director Dewey's tactics were unwise.
不明智
Unwise?
我们还在想办法
We're still trying to come
对外解释到底发生了什么
up with a narrative to explain what happened.
那个混蛋把铁手行动暴露在聚光灯下
That son of a bitch put a spotlight on Iron Hand.
把我们全都暴露了
On all of us.
卡鲁尔还没有对外说任何东西
Kalloor hasn't gone public yet.
我了解亚伦
I know Aaron.
我们还有其他办法可以和他周旋
There are still moves we can make with him.
说说看
Tell me.
杜威的问题在于 他属于过去
Dewey's problem was that he belonged in the past.
而卡鲁尔这样的人 正在塑造未来
People like Kalloor are shaping the future.
我了解这种人
These are my people.
我知道该怎么应付他
I know how to deal with him.
你想要什么
And what do you want?
你指派新的中情局局长时
When you appoint a new Agency Director,
你会希望他能听你的话
you're going to need someone working for your interests.
一个由你
Someone
授权之人
empowered by you.
那伯恩呢
What about Bourne?
你还是觉得 能把他带回来么
You still think you can bring him in?
他相信我
I have his trust.
毕竟我们经历了那么多
After what we went through.
我会带他回来的
I'll bring him in.
我有信心
I'm certain of it.
如果你做不到呢
And if you can't?
那就只能干掉他了
Then he'll have to be put down.
这个提议很有趣
It's an interesting proposal.
你可以停车了
You can pull over here.
当然 如果你认为
Of course, if you decide that
你不需要我 那就没问题了
you don't need me, then that's not a problem.
有许多机构会想知道我掌握的东西
There are many other agencies who would want what I know.
我带了东西给你
I brought you something.
这是你父亲在兰利纪念墙上的
It's a cast from your father's star,
银星的仿制品
on the Memorial Wall at Langley.
关于你的遭遇 我很遗憾
I'm sorry for what happened to you.
包括局里人是怎么对你的
How you were treated.
但是那些人都走了
But the people that did that are gone,
局里的局面已经和往日不一样了
and things are changing at the Agency.
你想怎么样
What is it you want?
我知道你是个爱国者
I know you've always been a patriot.
我知道你在乎这个国家经历着什么
That what happens to this country matters to you.
我们需要你帮忙保护我们
We need you to help protect us.
回来吧
Come back in.
我们一起努力
And we'll work together.
让我想想
Let me think about it.
我要怎么找你
How will I find you?
你还是觉得 你能把他带回来么
You still think you can bring him in?
他相信我
I have his trust.
毕竟我们经历了那么多
After what we went through.
我会带他回来的
I'll bring him in.
我有信心
I'm certain of it.
如果你做不到呢
And if you can't?
那就只能干掉他了
Then he'll have to be put down.